Sky Striker vs.
Kewl Tune.
Game 1.
Kewl Tune goes first.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Cue, then Special Summons Kewl Tune Rotary.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Track Maker.
Kewl Tune activates Rotary.
Cue becomes the next Chain Link, followed by Track Maker.
Kewl Tune adds Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck, then banishes Forbidden Crown from the Deck,
then adds Synchro from the Deck.
Kewl Tune activates Synchro, then adds Mix from the Deck.
Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Loudness War.
Kewl Tune activates JJ "Kewl Tune".
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Mix.
Kewl Tune activates Mix, then adds Cue from the Deck.
Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Remix.
Kewl Tune activates JJ, then sends Remix to the Graveyard, then adds Mix from the Deck.
Draw for turn.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!.
Sky Striker Mobilize - Linkage!
becomes the next Chain Link.
Draw for turn.
Sky Striker Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari.
Sky Striker adds Sky Striker Ace - Raye from the Deck.
Sky Striker activates Kagari, then recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Hayate using Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Special Maneuver - Lemnisgate!
, then returns Kagari to the Extra Deck, then returns Linkage to the Deck.
Sky Striker's Hayate attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Sky Striker activates Hayate, then sends Sky Striker Mecha - Shark Cannon from the Deck to the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Shizuku using Raye as material.
Sky Striker activates Lemnisgate, then banishes Lemnisgate.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace = Zero using Shizuku and Hayate as material.
Sky Striker activates Zero.
Kewl Tune chains Ghost Ogre & Snow Rabbit in response to destroy Zero.
Sky Striker adds Engage from the Deck.
Sky Striker activates Raye, then Special Summons Raye.
Sky Striker activates Raye, then Special Summons Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu.
Sky Striker activates Engage, then adds Raye from the Deck.
Sky Striker activates Engage, then adds Linkage from the Deck.
Sky Striker sets Forbidden Crown, then sets Linkage.
Draw for turn.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Mix.
Kewl Tune activates Mix.
Sky Striker activates Forbidden Crown on Mix, negating it and making it unable to attack, be
destroyed, be Tributed, or be used as Summon material this turn; it is also unaffected by
other activated effects.
Mix's effect is negated.
Kewl Tune activates JJ, then sends Loudness War to the Graveyard, then adds Cue from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Cue.
Sky Striker chains Ghost Belle & Haunted Mansion in response.
Cue's effect is negated.
Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Crackle.
Kewl Tune activates Cue.
Crackle becomes the next Chain Link.
Synchro banishes Super Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis.
Kewl Tune banishes Ghost Mourner & Moonlit Chill from the Deck.
Sky Striker returns Super Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis to the Extra Deck.
Draw for turn.
Sky Striker activates Linkage.
Sky Striker Mecha - Widow Anchor becomes the next Chain Link.
Sky Striker takes control of Crackle.
Sky Striker Special Summons Kagari.
Sky Striker activates Kagari, then recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker changes Crackle from face-up Defense Position to face-up Attack Position, then Normal Summons Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Zero using Raye and Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Zero, then recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker's Crackle attacks Mix, destroys it, and deals 700 damage.
Sky Striker's Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Kewl Tune regains control of Crackle.
Draw for turn.
Kewl Tune activates JJ, then sends Crackle to the Graveyard, then adds Kewl Tune Reco from the Deck.
Kewl Tune activates Crackle, then Special Summons Crackle, then banishes Albion the Branded Dragon.
Kewl Tune banishes Super Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Reco.
Kewl Tune activates Reco, then recovers Rotary from the Graveyard.
Kewl Tune activates Rotary.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Rotary.
Synchro Summons Track Maker.
Kewl Tune activates Rotary.
Track Maker becomes the next Chain Link.
Synchro adds Reco from the Deck.
Kewl Tune returns Ghost Belle & Haunted Mansion to the Deck.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Reco.
Synchro Summons Zalen the Shackled Dragon.
Kewl Tune activates Track Maker, then returns Zero to the Extra Deck.
Sky Striker activates Raye, then Special Summons Raye.
Kewl Tune's Zalen the Shackled Dragon attacks and destroys Raye.
Sky Striker returns Super Starslayer TY-PHON - Sky Crisis to the Extra Deck, then returns Albion
the Branded Dragon to the Extra Deck.
Draw for turn.
Sky Striker activates Engage, then adds Raye from the Deck, then draws Sky Striker Ace - Roze.
Sky Striker activates Engage, then adds Linkage from the Deck, then draws Widow Anchor.
Sky Striker activates Widow Anchor.
Linkage becomes the next Chain Link.
Sky Striker Special Summons Kagari.
Sky Striker takes control of Zalen the Shackled Dragon.
Sky Striker activates Kagari.
Roze becomes the next Chain Link.
Sky Striker Special Summons Roze.
Sky Striker recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Zero using Roze and Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Zero, then recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker activates The Fallen & The Virtuous, then sends Albion the Branded Dragon from the
Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Crackle.
Sky Striker's Zalen the Shackled Dragon attacks directly for 2800 damage.
Sky Striker's Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Sky Striker wins the duel.
Sky Striker wins Game 1.
Sky Striker vs.
Kewl Tune.
Game 2.
Kewl Tune goes first.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Kewl Tune Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Cue, then Special Summons Kewl Tune Rotary.
Kewl Tune activates Synchro Overtake, then Special Summons Kewl Tune Reco.
Kewl Tune activates Reco, then adds Kewl Tune Mix from the Deck.
Kewl Tune Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Track Maker.
Kewl Tune activates Rotary.
Track Maker becomes the next Chain Link.
Kewl Tune adds Mix from the Deck.
Kewl Tune adds Synchro from the Deck.
Kewl Tune activates Synchro, then adds Mix from the Deck.
Synchro Summons Kewl Tune RS.
Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Loudness War.
Synchro Summons Kewl Tune Remix.
Kewl Tune activates Cue, then banishes Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring from the Deck.
Synchro Summons Kewl Tune B2B.
Draw for turn.
Kewl Tune activates Maxx "C".
Sky Striker activates Sky Striker Mobilize - Engage!.
Kewl Tune chains Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring in response to negate Engage's Deck effect.
Sky Striker chains Radiant Typhoon Chant in response, then adds Radiant Typhoon Swen from the Deck,
then Mobilize - Engage!
's effect is negated.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Sky Striker Ace - Raye.
Sky Striker activates Raye, then Special Summons Sky Striker Ace - Kagari.
Kewl Tune draws Infinite Impermanence.
Sky Striker activates Kagari, then recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker activates Engage, then adds Raye from the Deck.
Sky Striker activates The Fallen & The Virtuous, then sends Albion the Branded Dragon from the
Extra Deck to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Loudness War.
Sky Striker activates Forbidden Droplet, then sends Swen from the hand to the Graveyard, then selects
B2B with Forbidden Droplet, negating its effects and halving its ATK until the end of the
turn.
Sky Striker's Kagari attacks B2B, destroys it, and deals 300 damage.
Sky Striker activates Albion the Branded Dragon, then adds Fallen & Virtuous from the Deck.
Draw for turn.
Kewl Tune sets Infinite Impermanence, then sets Dominus Purge.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Hayate using Kagari as material.
Sky Striker activates Radiant Typhoon Vision.
Kewl Tune chains Dominus Purge in response.
Radiant Vision's effect is negated.
Sky Striker's Hayate attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Sky Striker activates Hayate, then sends Sky Striker Mecha - Shark Cannon from the Deck to the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Kagari using Hayate as material.
Sky Striker activates Kagari.
Kewl Tune chains Infinite Impermanence in response.
Kagari's effect is negated.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace - Shizuku using Kagari as material.
Sky Striker Link Summons Sky Striker Ace = Zero using Raye and Shizuku as material.
Sky Striker activates Zero, then recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker activates Engage, then adds Raye from the Deck, then draws Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring.
Sky Striker sets Fallen & Virtuous.
Draw for turn.
Kewl Tune Normal Summons Cue.
Kewl Tune activates Cue.
Sky Striker chains Ash Blossom & Joyous Spring in response to negate Cue's Deck effect.
Cue's effect is negated.
Sky Striker activates Fallen & Virtuous, then sends Ecclesia and the Dark Dragon from the Extra
Deck to the Graveyard.
Fallen & Virtuous destroys Cue.
Draw for turn.
Sky Striker Normal Summons Raye.
Sky Striker Link Summons Kagari using Raye as material.
Sky Striker activates Kagari, then recovers Engage from the Graveyard.
Sky Striker Link Summons Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu using Kagari as material.
Sky Striker's Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Sky Striker's Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Draw for turn.
Sky Striker's Zero attacks directly for 2000 damage.
Sky Striker's Prototype Sky Striker Ace - Amatsu attacks directly for 1500 damage.
Sky Striker wins the duel.
Sky Striker wins Game 2.
Final score: Sky Striker 2–0.